Here is the situation. I am currently improving the way that people access documents within the HOA. For years, a management company has kept these documents on a portal that is VERY disorganized. It almost seems that it was intentionally. Some of these documents are valuable in terms of managing and using afforded rights within the HOA but other documents are, from what I can, wastes of paper. The kind of crap documentation that you put in a binder to confuse people. So....what are we doing. 

I am working on a grassroots HOA project. I have collected all of the documentation into one location. I am going to organize it for distribution. I will also be translating everything into 7 different langauges. I do not need you to do the translation piece right now. I tell you in case it helps you help me build the organization pattern. 

The data that you see below is the output of a tree /f command in PowerShell. The idea is that you can see all of the files that I have to organize. Please read the name of each file that has the extension .pdf. The name of the file should imply what the document is and its function. What I want you to do is provide a brief desription in English of each document. Tell me what it is, what it does, and why we have it. 

Once you have that done I need your help organizing this in a understandable format. It will all be uploaded to a webpage but I need to know what categories to put these in so people with not a lot of education can easily see and understand their purpose. 

You will see one directory called "repository". These are documents that I think are worthless. If I am wrong please indicate why I would be wrong and why I should include it in the posting. 

The last thing I have to comment here is about you asking questions. This is an extremely complex task. If you you are confused or I have information that can help you do a better job please tell me. 

The Data 

---------------------------------------------------
│   AlternativeDisputePolicy.pdf
│   ArticlesOfInc.pdf
│   ClubHouseRental.pdf
│   ConflictResolutionPolicy.pdf
│   CoventsConditionsRestrictions.pdf
│   FeedListForChatGPT.txt
│   InsuranceGuidelines.pdf
│   InsurancePolicy.pdf
│   InvestmentofReserves.pdf
│   MeetingPolicy.pdf
│   NewAssessmentNotice.pdf
│   NewsLetterSpring2023.pdf
│   ParkingRules.pdf
│   PoolRules.pdf
│   RecordsInspectionPolicy.pdf
│   RighofCollection.pdf
│   RightofEnforcement.pdf
│   RightsAndResponsibilities.pdf
│   Rules&Regulations.pdf
│   
└───Repository
        ACHFormX.pdf
        ColoredMap.pdf
        EngineeringDocuments.pdf
        FeedDisclosure.pdf
        FrontDoors.pdf
        ImprovementForm(ARC).pdf
        ImprovmentForm(ADR).pdf
        JewellStreetSiding.pdf
        OaklandStreetSiding.pdf
        OldReserveStuyFund.pdf
        OswegoStreetSiding.pdf
        PeoriaStreetSiding.pdf
        
